(Silence; Operating Room Area)
=Stand Up for Love=
=Episode 22=
Find out
who leaked this.
(Yes.)
(Should we calm the rumors?)
No.
Make it worse.
(Zhang Haotian.)
(It's time we settled our score.)
(The kidney your mother received)
(was taken from a girl)
(named Jiang Lai.)
(Your husband, Zhang Haotian,
deceived her with love.)
Baby,
who made you upset?
Two years ago, my mom was diagnosed
with kidney failure.
But recently,
our family doctor
searched the database
and found a perfectly matched kidney.
She refused to donate, no matter
how much we offered.
It's driving me crazy.
Can I see it?
(Kidney Function Test: Jiang Lai)
(I don't like Zhao Ke,)
(but I did want to know
what really happened.)
(Prenuptial Agreement)
(When I used my own life as leverage)
(and got the prenuptial agreement,)
(I found out Mom had set up
a trust fund.)
(Trust Fund Agreement)
(I was furious at the time.)
(I thought my mom kept placing)
(more and more restraints on Haotian.)
(It was seriously
affecting our marriage.)
(So I contacted the trustee.)
(Lulu.)
(Setting up the trust)
(was a desperate measure Ms. Su
took to protect you.)
(After my mom passed away,)
(Haotian framed me for cheating)
(to divorce me and split our assets.)
(Why are you here?)
(Get away from me!)
(Lulu.)
(Please let me go.)
(I opened the safe)
(and deliberately let Haotian
see the trust fund.)
(I wanted to see his reaction)
(when he realized he would get nothing.)
(But it turned out...)
(No surprise at all.)
(We can get divorced right now.)
(I really love you, Lulu.)
(Divorce would hurt me even more.)
(I can't imagine my life without you.)
(Instead of worrying about this,)
(you should look into)
(the truth)
(behind your mother's death.)
(Your mother's death)
(is connected to Zhang Haotian.)
(Whether Zhang Haotian was responsible)
(for my mother's death,)
(the police will find out.)
(But right now,)
(I'll use this illegal
fundraising scandal)
(to burn away your disguise.)
(Let me)
(be the last victim.)
Dr. Chen, can I have my phone back now?
Jiang Lai.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Do you know
I could
kill you here as easily
as snapping my fingers?
Mai.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Let's go.
Mr. Zhang,
I've invested a lot of money in you.
What about the 40% return you promised?
You can't go back on your word.
You're not leaving until you
give us an explanation.
You looked so respectable,
but you're nothing but a fraud.
You married Ms. Lin
just to get your hands on her money.
Could he have something to do
with Ms. Su's death?
You believe every rumor you hear.
You're just being used by someone.
Don't you know that?
When will my returns arrive?
I've invested for over two months.
And I haven't seen a single cent.
Give us our money back!
Investments come with risks.
You should all know that.
No returns mean you lost money.
If you want to take legal action,
go ahead.
Hello?
Hello, baby.
Can you possibly
transfer five hundred million
to me first?
Honey,
large transfers
can't possibly arrive in one day.
Okay.
(This is bad.)
(I'm screwed.)
Ke.
Come with me.
Chen Ping must have told you.
I'm not Zhao Ke.
I'm Jiang Lai.
You're Zhang Yongren's daughter.
We're family.
We still have a home.
A home?
Someone like you doesn't deserve one.
Let's go.
Jiang Lai.
You...
Don't hurt her.
Let go.
(Everything Is Exposed)
♪Listen, the wind chimes softly whisper♪
♪I should forget you♪
♪But I have the will,
yet not the strength♪
♪To carry on♪
♪The scenery you once longed to see♪
♪You no longer have the strength♪
♪You want me to go there for you♪
♪I look up and see a hollow sky♪
♪Your freedom♪
♪Has become my cage♪
♪My hand brushes over your smile
in the photograph♪
♪This glass of wine is filled
with sorrow♪
♪I look up at the beautiful night sky♪
♪You told me♪
♪I would shine like a star♪
♪But you forgot to teach me♪
♪How to live without you♪
♪I look up at the starry sky♪
♪So hazy and blurred♪